Historical Materials Collection UA136
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Photographs, 1819 -- 2009; UA136.002; 4.6 Linear Feet; 1 Artifact(s); 1412 Digital Object(s)
  - Photograph of Eaton Hall and campus, 1910; UA136.002.015.00035 (Box Shared 10)
    Hainen photo Co., Conneant.
  - Painting of Tufts campus, 1893 -- 1910; UA136.002.015.00036 (Box Shared 10)
    Littig & Co. The date is approximate, judged from the trolley and the clothing on the picture.
  - Faculty of Tufts College, Frank Fowle's copy, 1896; UA136.002.015.00037 (Box Shared 36)
    This photograph was retrieved from Ballou Hall, Spring 2010. The back of the mounting says 'Frank Fowle Personal' and is dated 1923.
  - Testimonial dinner, Dr. Harry Posner, Hotel Statler, Boston, Mass, 1952-06-14; UA136.002.015.00038; Fay Foto (Box Small Map Case 1 Drawer 1)
    This panoramic photograph was removed from the Harry Posner vertical file in the fall of 2011 and rehoused to address preservation concerns.
  - First class and faculty of Tufts College, 1857; UA136.002.017.00001 (Box Large Map Case 1 Drawer 1)
    Very fragile.
  - Class and faculty of Tufts College, 1857 -- 1867; UA136.002.018.00001 (Box Large Map Case 1 Drawer 1)
  - Award to Tufts College from the World's Columbian Commission, 1893; UA136.002.019.00001 (Box Large Map Case 1 Drawer 5)
    This poster was found uncatalogued in the stacks in summer 2008. It is located in an oversize folder in the map case. This award poster is evidence of Tufts College's participation in the college exhibits at the World's Columbian Exhibition in Chicago in 1893. The award states that Tufts' exhibit was an "illustration of college grounds, buildings, course of study, and appliances." They received the award "for excellence of course of study, buildings, and appliances for the work of a New England college." The college exhibits occupied space in the educational section of the Liberal Arts Department in the south gallery of the Manufactures and Liberal Arts Building. Apparently the purpose of these exhibits was to display the educational facilities, courses of study and methods of instruction afforded by the colleges. More information can be found by viewing the "Report of the Massachusetts Board of World's Fair Managers" (Boston, 1894). See also Columbian Exhibition memorabilia in the artifact collection.
  - Packard Hall near completion of 2009 renovations, 2009-04-09; UA136.002.025.00001; Lenehan, Jeannine
    Photo taken with a Nikon D60, as renovations to the building were being completed.
    Buildings; Trees
  - Photograph of Jumbo the elephant being washed, 1965 -- 1975; UA136.002.030.00001 (Box Shared 79)
  - 'Jumbo' movie promotion photograph, 1962; UA136.002.030.00002 (Box Shared 79)
    Taken in Syracuse, NY by Seymour Bellin, featuring Matthew, Jena, and Jeff Bellin.
  - Jackson College riders [equestrian], 1953; UA136.002.DO.00002; Unknown (Box Shared 43)
    8 x 10
    Athletics; Horse sports; People; Students; photographic print; photographic print; Jackson College
  - Jackson students sitting in a lounge, 1949; UA136.002.DO.00003; Unknown (Box Shared 83)
    Housing; Students; People; Interior views; photographic print; Jackson College
  - Goddard Chapel, 1950; UA136.002.DO.00108; Unknown (Box Shared 84)
    5 x 7
    Buildings; photographic print
  - Sylvanus Packard, UA136.002.DO.00119; Herwig, Ellis (Box Shared 27)
    People; Portraits; photographic print; Packard, Sylvanus
  - Women's tennis team, 1950; UA136.002.DO.00127; Unknown (Box Shared 26)
    5x7
    Tennis (Women's); Athletics; People; Students; photographic print; Jackson College
  - General Electric College Bowl, Jackson College, 1969; UA136.002.DO.00128; Waldinger, Conrad (Box Shared 27)
    Meg O'Donnell, J. Kemelhor, M. Carnell, Marcia Haley
    Events; Students; People; photographic print; O'Donnell, Meg; Kemelhor, J.; Carnell, M.; Haley, Marcia; Jackson College
  - Graduates of Tufts Divinity School, 1897; UA136.002.DO.00129; Unknown (Box Shared 27)
    8x10
    Students; People; photographic print; Bartlett, A.E.; Benton, H.E.; Bissell, F.M.; Earle, A. Gertrude; Eills, John; Footien, G.F.; Macduff, Belle S.; Robbins, C. Guy; Smith, John; Smith, Mrs. N.W.P.; Taylor, F.A.; Walker, F.S.; Divinity School; Crane Theological School
  - Students performing bible play they wrote, 1948; UA136.002.DO.00130; Duette Photographers (Box Shared 27)
    Identified on back: School of Religion, Summer workshop in religious education.
    Students; Costumes; Plays; photographic print; School of Religion
  - Students at Memorial Steps, 1950; UA136.002.DO.00131; Unknown (Box Shared 27)
    Students; People; photographic print
  - Trustees dinner, 1963; UA136.002.DO.00133; Duette (Box Shared 27)
    Events; People; College presidents; Faculty; photographic print; Wessell, Nils Yngve; Balch, Marston Stevens; Board of Trustees
  - Trustees dinner, October 26, 1967; UA136.002.DO.00134; Duette (Box Shared 27)
    People; photographic print; Board of Trustees
  - Lincoln Filene Center, 1960; UA136.002.DO.00135; Unknown (Box Shared 27)
    architectural sketch
    Buildings; photographic print; Lincoln Filene Center
  - Class in civic education at Natick High School, 1954; UA136.002.DO.00136; Duette (Box Shared 27)
    Students; People; photographic print; Lincoln Filene Center
  - Construction sign for Lincoln Filene Center, 1954; UA136.002.DO.00137; Unknown (Box Shared 27)
    7x7
  - Clean Air Car Race car and students, 1970; UA136.002.DO.00138; Unknown (Box Shared 26)
  - Engineering field work, 1903 -- 1904; UA136.002.DO.00139; Unknown (Box Shared 26)
    Students; People; photographic print; College of Engineering
  - McIlroy Fluid Network Analyzer analog computer, 1958; UA136.002.DO.00140; Unknown (Box Shared 27)
    People; Computers; photographic print; Dept. of Mechanical Engineering
  - Foundry in Power House Extension, 1904; UA136.002.DO.00141; Stebbins, N.L. (Box Shared 27)
  - Students studying, 1960; UA136.002.DO.00142; Unknown (Box Shared 27)
    Students; People; photographic print; Library
  - Tufts Humanities Group, 1965; UA136.002.DO.00143; Duette (Box Shared 27)
    Faculty; People; photographic print; Milburn, Nancy; Humanities Group
  - Homecoming King and Queen, 1980; UA136.002.DO.00279; Unknown (Box Shared 85)
    Events; photographic print
  - Baseball Team, UA136.002.DO.00280; Unknown (Box Shared 85)
    Athletics; Baseball; photographic print
  - Otto Raspe, 1906; UA136.002.DO.00281; Unknown (Box Shared 85)
    Cabinet Card
    People; photographic print
  - Ethel M. Hayes, 1891; UA136.002.DO.00282; Horner (Box Shared 86)
    5 photo mounted on 4.25 x 6.5 card. Hayes attended Tufts College 1892-1896.
    Women; Students; Portraits; photographic print; Hayes, Ethel M.
  - Audrey Hale, 1995; UA136.002.DO.00283; Morelli, Mark (Box Shared 85)
    People; photographic print; Hale, Audrey; Tufts University
  - Seymour O. Simches, 1977; UA136.002.DO.00284; Unknown (Box Shared 85)
    People; Ceremonial Maces; photographic print; Simches, Seymour O.; Dept. of Romance Languages; Faculty of Arts and Sciences
  - Marjorie. B. Greene, UA136.002.DO.00285; Unknown (Box Shared 86)
    People; photographic print; Greene, Marjorie B.
  - Victor Alonzo Prather, 1947; UA136.002.DO.00286; Unknown (Box Vertical File Cabinets)
    25. In Victor Alonzo Prather vertical file.
    Alumni and alumnae; Navy V-12 Program; photographic print; Prather, Victor
  - Earle F. Littleton, UA136.002.DO.00287; Duette (Box Shared 86)
    People; photographic print; Littleton, Earle F.
  - Earle F. Littleton, UA136.002.DO.00288; Unknown (Box Shared 86)
  - Moses True Brown, UA136.002.DO.00290; Unknown (Box Shared 85)
    People; photographic print; Brown, Moses True
  - Harry P. Burden, 1953; UA136.002.DO.00291; Duette (Box Shared 86)
    People; photographic print; Burden, Harry Poole
  - Mabel. W. Daniels, 1933; UA136.002.DO.00292; Garo (Box Shared 85)
    H 20.5, W 13 cm
    People; photographic print; Daniels, Mabel Wheeler
  - Anna Quincy Churchill, 1917; UA136.002.DO.00293; Horner, Carl J. (Box Shared 86)
    3.5 x 6
    People; photographic print; Churchill, Anna Quincy
  - Frank W. Durkee, 1889; UA136.002.DO.00295; Unknown (Box Shared 85)
    H 16.5, W 21.5 cm
    People; photographic print; Durkee, Frank W
  - Henrietta Brown Durkee, 1918; UA136.002.DO.00296; Unknown (Box Shared 86)
    This date is approximate.
    Women; Portraits; photographic print; Durkee, Henrietta Noble Brown
  - James V. Elliott, 1976; UA136.002.DO.00298; Ellis Herwig Photography (Box Shared 85)
    People; photographic print; Elliott, James Vance
  - Alexander Elias, UA136.002.DO.00299; Unknown (Box Shared 86)
    5
    People; photographic print; Elias, Alexander
  - Luis de Florez, 1946; UA136.002.DO.00300; Geller, David (Box Shared 85)
  - Donald A. Cowdery, 1939; UA136.002.DO.00301; Unknown (Box Shared 86)
    3 x 4
    People; photographic print; Cowdery, Donald A.
  - Benjamin Graves Brown, UA136.002.DO.00302; Unknown (Box Shared 85)
    People; photographic print; Brown, Benjamin G.
  - Anne Borghesani, UA136.002.DO.00303; Unknown (Box Shared 86)
  - William Frank Wyatt, UA136.002.DO.00305; Unknown (Box Shared 86)
    3.5 x 4
  - Max Tishler, 1960; UA136.002.DO.00306; Unknown (Box Shared 85)
    H 20.5, W 12.5 cm
  - Charles E. Stearns, UA136.002.DO.00307; Unknown (Box Shared 86)
  - William Howell Reed, 1916; UA136.002.DO.00308; Bachrach (Box Shared 86)
  - Robert L. Nichols, UA136.002.DO.00309; Unknown (Box Shared 86)
  - Russell E. Miller, 1978; UA136.002.DO.00310; Southwick, Peter (Box Shared 85)
  - Lewis F. Manly, 1930; UA136.002.DO.00311; Unknown (Box Shared 86)
  - John Gibson, UA136.002.DO.00313; Unknown (Box Shared 86)
    2 x 2
  - Daniel Ounjian, 1985; UA136.002.DO.00314; Unknown (Box Shared 86)
  - Audrey Butvay Gruss, UA136.002.DO.00315; Gibbons, Catherine (Box Shared 86)
  - Michael Autges, UA136.002.DO.00316; Unknown (Box Shared 86)
  - Paula Frazier Poskitt, UA136.002.DO.00327
    People
  - Joseph Neubauer, UA136.002.DO.00328
    Original print returned to Trustees Office
  - Norbert Wiener, 1925; UA136.002.DO.00329
    Found in "Norbert Wiener: Collected Works Volume I"
  - Howard Sample, 1967; UA136.002.DO.00330
  - Theresa McDermott Carzo, UA136.002.DO.00331; Unknown (Box Shared 86)
    75
  - Amos Dolbear, 1880; UA136.002.DO.00334; Unknown (Box Shared 85)
    9 x 6
    People; Portraits; Faculty; photographic print; Dolbear, Amos Emerson; College of Engineering
  - Leonard Carmichael,1938-1970, UA136.002.DO.00335; Unknown (Box Shared 86)
    Portraits; People; photographic print; Carmichael, Leonard; Office of the President
  - Lloyd Trefethen, 1990; UA136.002.DO.00336
    Original print returned to subject
    People; Portraits
  - Robert J. Manning, 1983; UA136.002.DO.00337; Unknown
    "Official Navy Photograph Not for Publication Unless Officially Released"
  - Charles Bludhorn, UA136.002.DO.00338; Unknown (Box Shared 86)
    3 x 3
    People; Portraits; photographic print
  - Marianne Whitherby, 1999; UA136.002.DO.00339; Unknown (Box Shared 86)
    3.5 x 5
  - Jeanette P. Lerman, UA136.002.DO.00340; Unknown (Box Shared 86)
  - Jester Hairston, 1994; UA136.002.DO.00341
    People; Portraits; Hairston, Jester; Department of Music
  - Stephen J. Sapuppo, UA136.002.DO.00342
    Original print returned to owner.
  - J. and S. Stone, UA136.002.DO.00343; Unknown (Box Shared 86)
  - Ivan Galantic, UA136.002.DO.00344; Unknown (Box Shared 86)
  - Jane Herman, UA136.002.DO.00345; Unknown (Box Shared 86)
  - Melissa Meyers, UA136.002.DO.00346; Meyers, William
    Copyright William Meyers, 180 Riverside Dr. #3A New York, NY 10024-1047
  - Elizabeth V. Tischler, 2000; UA136.002.DO.00347; Unknown (Box Shared 86)
  - Albert Imlah, 1965; UA136.002.DO.00349
    Jumbo Book, 1965, p. 136.
  - Toivo Laminan, 1931; UA136.002.DO.00350
    From Jumbo Book, 1931, p. 45.
  - Marston Balch in front of the Arena Theater, UA136.002.DO.00351; Unknown (Box Shared 88)
    Buildings; Theaters; photographic print; Balch, Marston Stevens
  - Charles Neal Barney, UA136.002.DO.00352; Unknown (Box Shared 88)
    7.5 x 9
    People; photographic print; Barney, Charles Neal
  - Arland A. Dirlam, UA136.002.DO.00353; Unknown (Box Shared 86)
    People; Alumni and alumnae; photographic print; Dirlam, Arland A.
  - Henry J. Braker, UA136.002.DO.00354; Unknown (Box Shared 88)
    People; photographic print; Braker, Henry Jones
  - Cora Polk Dewick, 1952; UA136.002.DO.00355; Duette (Box Shared 88)
    People; Alumni and alumnae; photographic print; Dewick, Cora Polk
  - Heman A. Dearborn, 1891; UA136.002.DO.00357; Davis and Dow (Box Shared 88)
    cabinet card
    People; Alumni and alumnae; photographic print; Dearborn, Heman A.
  - Stearns Village, UA136.002.DO.00358; Unknown (Box Shared 88)
    Buildings; World War, 1939-1945; photographic print
  - Wives Club Stearns Village, UA136.002.DO.00359; Unknown (Box Shared 88)
  - Stearns Village Wives Club Party, UA136.002.DO.00360; Unknown (Box Shared 88)
  - Mt. Fay (North Face), 1974; UA136.002.DO.00382; Gill, Jack; Joseph, Jim (Box Shared 88)
    Mountains; photographic print
  - Mellen House, 1954; UA136.002.DO.00385; Unknown (Box Shared 86)
    RNCH1
    Buildings; Houses; photographic print
  - West Hall, UA136.002.DO.00387; Unknown (Box Shared 88)
    Buildings; Dormitories; photographic print
  - Railroad Station at Tufts, UA136.002.DO.00388; Unknown (Box Shared 86)
    Buildings; Railroad stations; photographic print
  - Leonard, Dr. Charles H., UA136.002.DO.00389; Unknown (Box Shared 88)
    People; photographic print; Leonard, Charles H.
  - Metcalf Hall, UA136.002.DO.00405; Unknown (Box Shared 86)
  - Crane Theological School [Paige-Miner], UA136.002.DO.00406; Duette (Box Shared 50)
    Buildings; photographic print; Crane Theological School; Divinity School
  - Miner Hall, UA136.002.DO.00407; Unknown (Box Shared 86)
  - Mugar Hall, UA136.002.DO.00408; Macone, Allessandro (Box Shared 50)
    Food service; Buildings; Academic; photographic print
  - Paige Hall, 1892; UA136.002.DO.00409; Unknown (Box Shared 50)
    Buildings; Academic; photographic print
  - James D. Hume, 1995; UA136.002.DO.00410
    People; Portraits; Hume, James D.
  - Mary Grant Charles, 1962; UA136.002.DO.00411
    People; Charles, Mary Grant
  - Donald A. Cowdery, 1939; UA136.002.DO.00412
    People; Portraits; Cowdery, Donald A.
  - Nancy Anderson, 1992; UA136.002.DO.00413
    People; Portraits; Anderson, Nancy W.
  - Mary Grant Charles, UA136.002.DO.00414
    People; Portraits; Charles, Mary Grant
  - Howard Sample, 1987; UA136.002.DO.00415
    People; Sample, Howard
  - Haskell, Harold C., UA136.002.DO.00416; Unknown (Box Shared 50)
    People; Alumni and alumnae; photographic print; Haskell, Harold Clifford
  - The Reservoir, Tufts College, 1883; UA136.002.DO.00417; Unknown (Box Shared 50)
    Reservoirs; photographic print
  - Tufts Golf Course, UA136.002.DO.00418; Lawlor, Dave (Box Shared 50)
    Athletics; Golf; photographic print
  - Cannon near Goddard Chapel, UA136.002.DO.00419; Duette (Box Shared 50)
    Monuments; Events; photographic print
  - Dr. Walter Hall, UA136.002.DO.00420; Unknown (Box Shared 89)
    4 x 6
    People; photographic print; Hall, Walter Langdon
  - Houston Hall, UA136.002.DO.00421; Unknown (Box Shared 50)
    Buildings; Dormitories; photographic print; Houston, Clarence P.
  - Howe Mechanical Engineering Building, 1957; UA136.002.DO.00422; Duette (Box Shared 50)
    Buildings; photographic print; Dept. of Mechanical Engineering
  - Gravity Stone, UA136.002.DO.00423; Unknown (Box Shared 50)
    Monuments; photographic print
  - Hodgdon Hall, UA136.002.DO.00424; Duette (Box Shared 50)
  - Cousens Gymnasium, 1952; UA136.002.DO.00426; Unknown (Box Shared 50)
    10 x 8
    Athletics; Buildings; Gymnasiums; photographic print; Cousens, John Albert
  - War Memorial Steps, UA136.002.DO.00427; Unknown (Box Shared 50)
    Memorials; photographic print
  - Fischer Arcade, UA136.002.DO.00428; Unknown (Box Shared 50)
    Buildings; photographic print; Crane Theological School
  - Miller Hall, UA136.002.DO.00429; Unknown (Box Shared 50)
  - Golf Course, UA136.002.DO.00430; Unknown (Box Shared 89)
    4 x 5
  - The "Bubbler" next to Packard Hall [College Pump], 1899; UA136.002.DO.00431; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 89)
    4x3 and 3x5 copy negative
    Fountains; photographic print
  - Elmore MacPhie, UA136.002.DO.00432; Bachrach (Box Shared 90)
    People; Alumni and alumnae; photographic print; MacPhie, Elmore I.; Board of Trustees
  - Dr. A. Warren Stearns, UA136.002.DO.00434; Bachrach (Box Shared 89)
    People; Alumni and alumnae; photographic print; Stearns, Albert Warren; School of Medicine
  - Dr. Albert Nott [first dean of Tufts Medical School], UA136.002.DO.00435; Unknown (Box Shared 89)
    People; Faculty; photographic print; Nott, Albert; School of Medicine
  - John Tilton, UA136.002.DO.00436; Duette (Box Shared 89)
    People; Faculty; College administrators; photographic print; Tilton, John Philip
  - Lauro Cavazos, UA136.002.DO.00437; Unknown (Box Shared 89)
    People; photographic print; Cavazos, Lauro
  - Joseph M. Hayman [Dean, School of Medicine 1953-1966], 1967; UA136.002.DO.00438; Unknown (Box Shared 89)
    People; photographic print; Hayman, Joseph M.
  - Katherine Jeffers, UA136.002.DO.00439; Duette (Box Shared 89)
    People; College administrators; photographic print; Jeffers, Katherine Rosetta
  - Arthur Coolidge, UA136.002.DO.00440; Unknown (Box Shared 89)
    People; Alumni and alumnae; photographic print; Coolidge, Arthur W.
  - Frederick C. Hodgdon, UA136.002.DO.00441; White Studio (Box Shared 90)
    People; Alumni and alumnae; photographic print; Hodgdon, Frederick C.
  - Robert Meserve with Ballou Medal, UA136.002.DO.00442; Unknown (Box Shared 90)
    People; Medals; Ballou Medal for Distinguished Service; Alumni and alumnae; photographic print; Meserve, Robert W.; Board of Trustees
  - Etta Phillips MacPhie, 1967; UA136.002.DO.00443; Duette (Box Shared 89)
    People; Alumni and alumnae; photographic print; MacPhie, Etta; Board of Trustees
  - Haskell [Hall], September 16, 1965; UA136.002.DO.00444; Zimberg, George (Box Shared 90)
  - Goddard Gymnasium, 1892; UA136.002.DO.00445; Unknown (Box Shared 90)
    Buildings; Gymnasiums; photographic print
  - Hill [Hall], UA136.002.DO.00446; Unknown (Box Shared 90)
  - Hooper Infirmary, UA136.002.DO.00447; Unknown (Box Shared 90)
    5 x 8
    Buildings; Houses; photographic print; Health Services
  - Pearson Memorial Laboratory, 1948; UA136.002.DO.00448; Lawlor, Dave (Box Shared 90)
    Buildings; photographic print; Dept. of Chemistry
  - Robert Meserve-Tufts Trustee, UA136.002.DO.00449; Bachrach (Box Shared 90)
    People; Alumni and alumnae; photographic print; Meserve, Robert W.; Board of Trustees
  - Mrs. E. MacPhie, WA'13 H'76 [Etta Phillips MacPhie], 1976; UA136.002.DO.00450; Herwig, Ellis (Box Shared 90)
  - Frederick C. Hodgdon as a senior at Tufts College, 1894; UA136.002.DO.00452; Conly, C.F. (Box Shared 90)
  - Interior of Bray Mechanical Engineering Laboratory, 1957; UA136.002.DO.00453; Duette (Box Shared 90)
  - Bush Hall, UA136.002.DO.00454; Duette (Box Shared 90)
  - [Alumni House], UA136.002.DO.00455; Duette (Box Shared 90)
    Buildings; Houses; photographic print; Alumni Relations
  - [Alumnae Hall], UA136.002.DO.00456; Duette (Box Shared 90)
  - Hill [Hall], October, 1968; UA136.002.DO.00457; Unknown (Box Shared 89)
  - Goddard Gymnasium, UA136.002.DO.00458; Unknown (Box Shared 89)
    5 x 4
  - Goddard Gymnasium, 1887; UA136.002.DO.00459; Unknown (Box Shared 90)
  - Goddard Gymnasium and Dean Hall, 1892; UA136.002.DO.00460; Unknown (Box Shared 90)
    Gymnasiums; Dormitories; Buildings; photographic print
  - Capen House, UA136.002.DO.00461; Unknown (Box Shared 90)
  - Edith L. Bush, Dean of Jackson College 1925-1952, UA136.002.DO.00462; Unknown (Box Shared 89)
    People; Academic; Alumni and alumnae; College administrators; photographic print; Bush, Edith L.; Jackson College
  - Reservoir from College Hall, 1887; UA136.002.DO.00463; Adams and Aldrich
    in Tufts College 1887
    Reservoirs
  - Henry H. Banks, UA136.002.DO.00465; Gleason, David King
    in COE
    People; Academic; Alumni and alumnae; College administrators; Banks, Henry H.; School of Medicine; Dept. of Orthopedic Surgery
  - Wright House, 1954; UA136.002.DO.00466; Unknown (Box Shared 89)
    in RNCH2
  - Herbert Black, n.d, UA136.002.DO.00467; Unknown (Box Shared 90)
    7 x 9
    People; Alumni and alumnae; photographic print; Black, Herbert
  - Eugen B. Bowen (Oldest alum), 1951; UA136.002.DO.00470; Duette (Box Shared 90)
    People; Alumni and alumnae; photographic print; Bowen, Eugene B.
  - SS Tufts Victory, 1945; UA136.002.DO.00472; Unknown (Box Shared 90)
    Ships; photographic print; SS Tufts Victory
  - Student Body taking exams in Cousens Gym during World War II, 1943; UA136.002.DO.00473; Unknown (Box Shared 90)
    World War, 1939-1945; Students; photographic print
  - World War II group, 1943; UA136.002.DO.00474; Unknown (Box Shared 89)
    World War, 1939-1945; People; photographic print
  - Tufts band and World War II naval officers, 1943; UA136.002.DO.00475; Davis, Dwight (Box Shared 90)
    People; World War, 1939-1945; photographic print
  - John Porter Marshall, A.M. Professor of Chemistry, Mineralogy and Geology, 1872; UA136.002.DO.00477; Unknown (Box Shared 90)
    People; Faculty; College administrators; photographic print; Marshall, John P.; Board of Trustees; Dept. of Geology
  - Earle Littleton, Civil Engineering, Trustee, UA136.002.DO.00478; Unknown (Box Shared 89)
    People; Faculty; College administrators; photographic print; Littleton, Earle F.; Dept. of Civil Engineering; Board of Trustees
  - Bray Laboratory (Mechanical Engineering), UA136.002.DO.00479; Davis, Dwight (Box Shared 91)
  - Gager Gate, UA136.002.DO.00480; Unknown (Box Shared 91)
    Gates; Memorials; photographic print
  - Tufts Yacht Club, 1962; UA136.002.DO.00481; Duette (Box Shared 91)
    Athletics; Sailing; photographic print
  - Graves House as Delta Tau Delta Chapter house, 1915; UA136.002.DO.00487; Unknown (Box Shared 89)
    4.5 x 4
    Buildings; Housing; Greek letter societies; photographic print; Delta Tau Delta
  - D.U. [Delta Upsilon] Tufts, 1887; UA136.002.DO.00488; Unknown (Box Shared 91)
    Greek letter societies; photographic print; Hayes, Henry W.; Snow, Alva E.; Fairbanks, Wilson L.; Valdes, Clement; White, True W.; Melchor, Frank O.; Delta Upsilon
  - Zeta Psi, 1884; UA136.002.DO.00490; Unknown (Box Shared 91)
    Greek letter societies; People; Students; photographic print; Darling, Charles H.; Dana, Alston W.; Priest, Ira A.; Kendall, Fred O.; Day, Elias E.; Zeta Psi
  - John P. Marshall, Acting President, 1861; UA136.002.DO.00491; Clark, W. Loring (Box Shared 89)
    People; College administrators; photographic print; Marshall, John P.; Office of the President; Dept. of Chemistry
  - Chi Omega, 1947; UA136.002.DO.00492; Duette (Box Shared 91)
    Buildings; Housing; Greek letter societies; photographic print; Chi Omega
  - Tufts Boat Club on the Mystic River near Medford Square, 1874; UA136.002.DO.00495; Unknown (Box Shared 91)
    Athletics; Crew; photographic print
  - Tufts Boat Club [Boat House] on the Mystic River near Medfrod Square, 1874; UA136.002.DO.00496; Unknown (Box Shared 91)
  - Zeta Psi House of Tufts College, UA136.002.DO.00497; Unknown (Box Shared 89)
    Buildings; Housing; photographic print; Zeta Psi
  - Dewick Dining Room, UA136.002.DO.00498; Unknown (Box Shared 91)
    Image of Dewick Dining Hall when Dewick and Macphie dining halls were separate units. View is towards the Latin Way entrance; stairwell in the back of the photo leads to Latin Way and connection to Bush Hall.
    Food service; People; Students; photographic print